exercisetv.tv 2011-05-28

# Privacy Policy - About - ExerciseTV

## Privacy Practices and Feedback

This statement discloses the privacy practices for this website only, including an explanation of:

  * the categories of personally identifiable information about you that may be collected;
  * how the information is used; 
  * the categories of persons or entities with whom the information may be shared; 
  * the choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information; 
  * how you can opt in or out of ExerciseTV promotional e-mail; 
  * the kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information; 
  * how you can review and request changes to the information; 
  * how we notify visitors and users of this website of changes to this privacy statement; and 
  * the privacy policies that apply to subscribers to each ExerciseTV product and service.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to ExerciseTV through one of the Contact Us forms you will find on the Web site, or by sending a notice by U.S. Mail to:

ExerciseTV  
11611 San Vicente Blvd #505  
Los Angeles, Ca 90049  
Attention: ExerciseTV / Programming Privacy Feedback. 

or email us at [infotv@exercisetv.tv](mailto:infotv@exercisetv.tv)

## Information Collection and Use

A special note about children: ExerciseTV does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen and does not wish to collect any such information. Federal law requires website operators who collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen to first get parental consent. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, e-mail addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else.

## What categories of personally identifiable information do we collect?

The information collected by ExerciseTV falls into two categories: (1) information voluntarily supplied by visitors to and users of the website and (2) tracking information recorded as visitors and users navigate through the website. Some of this information is personally identifiable information, but much of it is not. Personally identifiable information is information that identifies a particular person. 

To make use of some features on our website visitors and users need to register and provide certain information as part of the registration process. We may ask, for example, for your name, e-mail address, street address and zip code. In addition, we may ask you for information about your interests in television viewing, sports, personal finance, the performing arts, and the like. The information you supply will help us to offer you more personalized features, complete the particular function of the website you are using, and tailor our website to your interests to make it more useful to you. Our systems will remember some of this information the next time you log in and use our website, but you can always review and change your information by following the instructions below under Changes to Information in this statement. The more you tell us about yourself, the more value we can offer you. Supplying this information is entirely voluntary. But if you choose not to supply the information, we may be unable to provide you with the products and services we make available to other users of and visitors to our website. And you will not be able to order selected products or services, or automate payments, over our website unless you provide certain personally identifiable information about yourself. When you submit any personally identifiable information over this website, ExerciseTV (i) will use the information for the purposes described at the time you submit it (for example, your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address provided while ordering one of our products or services will be used in connection with the processing and fulfillment of your order) and (ii) may use the information to contact you to make you aware of other products and services of interest. Of course, if you want to remain completely anonymous, you're still free to take advantage of the publicly available content on our website without registration.

## What categories of persons or entities do we share personally identifiable information with?

We consider the personally identifiable information contained in our business records to be confidential. We may sometimes disclose personally identifiable information about you to our affiliates or to others who work for us. We may also disclose personally identifiable information about you to service providers and vendors, and to others who provide products and services to us. For example, when you use certain functions on this website you may notice that the website actually collecting or processing the information may be other than a ExerciseTV website. We may be required by law or legal process to disclose certain personally identifiable information about you to lawyers and parties in connection with litigation and to law enforcement personnel. For example, we may be required by law to disclose personally identifiable information about you without your consent and without notice in order to comply with a valid legal process such as a subpoena, court order, or search warrant. What do we do to personalize your use of this website? To help make our website more responsive to the needs of our users and visitors, we use a standard feature of browser software called a "cookie." We use cookies to help us tailor our website to your needs, to deliver a better, more personalized service, and to remember certain choices you've made so you don't have to re-enter them. We use two kinds of cookies: (i) temporary or "session"-based cookies that contain certain information about a user's or visitor's use of our website at a particular time and (ii) "persistent" cookies that contain certain account-related information about a registered user's use of our website. Session-based cookies are automatically disabled or deleted when a user of or visitor to our website closes his or her browser software at the end of session. Persistent cookies remain stored on a registered user's computer system until he or she disables or deletes them. Of course, if you set your browser not to accept cookies or you delete them, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other visitors to and users of our website. 

The cookies we use don't directly identify visitors to or users of our website as particular persons. Rather, they contain information sufficient to simplify and improve a visitor's or user's experience on our website. For example, we may use session-based cookies to track the pages on our website visited by our users. We can build a better website if we know which pages our users are visiting and how often. Or, we may use persistent cookies to simplify access to a user's account information over our website, for example. 

In connection with the standard operation of ExerciseTV systems, certain non-personally identifiable information about visitors to this website is recorded. This information is used primarily to tailor and enhance visitors' experience using the website. We may use this information in an aggregate, non-personally identifiable form to, among other things, measure the use of our website and determine which products and services are the most popular with website visitors. Where do we permit visitors and users to opt in or out of ExerciseTV promotional e-mail? You may choose to receive promotional e-mails about ExerciseTV and other services by going to forms on the Internet web page located at www.exercisetv.tv and following the instructions there. If you have otherwise provided your e-mail address to ExerciseTV, or ExerciseTV has already obtained it, then ExerciseTV may have already contacted you about receiving promotional e-mails separately. 

Additionally, every promotional e-mail sent by ExerciseTV will contain opt-out instructions and contact information.

## Community Message Board

While the administrators and moderators of this forum will attempt to remove or edit any generally objectionable material as quickly as possible, it is impossible to review every message. Therefore all participants acknowledge that all posts made to these forums express the views and opinions of the author and not the administrators, moderators or webmaster (except for posts by these people) and hence will not be held liable.

All participants agree not to post any abusive, obscene, vulgar, slanderous, hateful, threatening, sexually-oriented or any other material that may violate any applicable laws. Doing so may lead to you being immediately and permanently banned (and your service provider being informed). The IP address of all posts is recorded to aid in enforcing these conditions. You agree that the webmaster, administrator and moderators of this forum have the right to remove, edit, move or close any topic at any time should they see fit. As a user you agree to any information you have entered above being stored in a database. While this information will not be disclosed to any third party without your consent the webmaster, administrator and moderators cannot be held responsible for any hacking attempt that may lead to the data being compromised.

This forum system uses cookies to store information on your local computer. These cookies do not contain any of the information you have entered above; they serve only to improve your viewing pleasure. The e-mail address is used only for confirming your registration details and password (and for sending new passwords should you forget your current one).

All registrants to the community message board agree to be bound by these conditions.

## Other Websites

To make our website more valuable to our visitors, we may offer some features in conjunction with other providers. Our website may also include links to other websites whose privacy policies and practices we don't control. Once you leave our website by linking to another one (you can tell where you are by checking the address known as a URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the website you're visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these websites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the website directly for more information.

## Security

All information gathered on our website is stored within an ExerciseTV-controlled database accessible only to ExerciseTV and its specifically authorized contractors and vendors. However, as effective as any security measure implemented by ExerciseTV may be, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the complete security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. If you don't want us to know any particular information about you, don't include it in anything that you submit or post to this website or send to us in e-mail.

## Changes to Information

You may review and change information that you provide to us through this website by returning to the pages where you entered it, and reviewing or changing the information directly. Changes to this Privacy Statement We may change this privacy statement from time to time. If we change this privacy statement at some point in the future, we'll post the changes on our website and by continuing to use the website after we post any changes; you accept and agree to this privacy statement, as modified. Of course, our use of information gathered while the current privacy statement is in effect will be consistent with the current statement, even if we change that statement later.

## Privacy Policies for ExerciseTV Products and Services

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for this website only. You may also view these privacy notices at www.exercisetv.tv at any time by clicking on the link for the privacy notice you wish to read. Effective: January 1, 2007.
